creare-webdesign.co.uk 2012-08-03

# Privacy Policy - Creare Group

Home » Privacy Policy

## Information Collection & Use

Creare is the sole owner of the information collected on this web site. We will not sell or share this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Creare collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

We request information from the user on our enquiry forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name, email and telephone numbers etc). This information is used to fulfil customer's enquiries and/or orders. We might get back to the customer to provide the information requested by the customer (such as a quote).

## Online Website Security

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our accounting staff or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

## Outgoing External Links

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. Creare is not responsisble for the information, content or opinions contained on external websites, including those of our clients.

## Choice/Opt-out

If you use this site to purchase services you may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications on our order form. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our companies may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us directly.

Users of our site are notified when their information is being collected or used by any third parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an third party, or not.
